const questions ={
  question: "What year did Episode VI: Return of the Jedi release in North American theatres?",
  options: {
    a: "1977",
    b: "1980",
    c: "1983",
    d: "1986",
  },
  correctAnswer: "c"
},

{
  question: "What (were) the names of Luke's Aunt and Uncle",
  options: {
    a: "Padme and Anakin Skywalker",
    b: "Owen and Beru Lars",
    c: "George and Marcia Lucas",
    d: "Harrison Ford and Peter Mayhew",
  },
  correctAnswer: "b"
},

{
  question: "What is Chewbacca's home planet?",
  options: {
    a: "Dantooine",
    b: "Dathomir",
    c: "Corellia",
    d: "Kashyyyk",
  },
  correctAnswer: "d"
},

{
  question: "How many parsecs did it take?",
  options: {
    a: "less than 10 parsecs",
    b: "less than 12 parsecss",
    c: "About 14 parsecs",
    d: "Han Solo never made the Kessel Run, it is just a story he made up to kiss princesses",
  },
  correctAnswer: "b"
},

{
  question: "What is the species name of the creature in Jabba the Hutt's palace dungeon?",
  options: {
    a: "Sarlac",
    b: "Rancor",
    c: "Oliphaunt",
    d: "Rathtar",
  },
  correctAnswer: "b"
},

{
  question: "Who was Qui-Gon Jinn's direct master when he was as a padawan?",
  options: {
    a: "Count Dooku",
    b: "Self taught",
    c: "Silas Portrun",
    d: "Sifo-Dyas",
  },
  correctAnswer: "a"
},

{
  question: "What species is Watto, the junk-dealing slave-owner from Episode I/II",
  options: {
    a: "Cad-Baneian",
    b: "Thrawnian",
    c: "Toydarian",
    d: "Twi'lek",
  },
  correctAnswer: "c"
},

{
  question: "What planet does Luke travel to in order to get training from Master Yoda?",
  options: {
    a: "Dagobah",
    b: "Dantooine",
    c: "Yavin IV",
    d: "Hoth",
  },
  correctAnswer: "a"
},

{
  question: "Who is the only member to sit on the Jedi Council and not achieve the rank of Master?",
  options: {
    a: "Anakin Skywalker",
    b: "Luke Skywalker",
    c: "Qui-Gonn Jinn",
    d: "TAKE A SEAT, YOUNG SKYWALKER",
  },
  correctAnswer: "a"
},

{
  question: "What was the intended title for Episode VI prior to 'Return of the Jedi'?",
  options: {
    a: "Revenge of the Jedi",
    b: "Attack of the Sith",
    c: "A Newer Hope",
    d: "",
  },
  correctAnswer: "a"
},
